https://powerobjects.com/privacy-policy/

PowerCare Login|Careers|Our Response to Covid-19
ProductsPower PlatformPower BIPower AppsPower AutomateMicrosoft Dynamics 365SalesMarketingField ServiceCustomer ServiceFinanceCommerceHuman ResourcesProject Service AutomationBusiness CentralMicrosoft Dynamics AXMicrosoft Dynamics CRMOffice 365PowerPacksIndustriesFinancial ServicesPowerBankingPowerCapitalPowerInsuranceHealth and Life SciencesLocal and Regional GovernmentManufacturingOil and GasPropertyPowerPropertyRetail/CPGUtilitiesServicesDynamics 365 ERP ApplicationsDynamics 365 CRM ApplicationsMigration from AX to D365PowerSuccessLicensing/CSPChange ManagementSupportPay-as-you-Go SupportDedicated Support EngineerApplication Support ManagementOnline AcceleratorPowerSuccess for Business CentralPowerSuccess D365 CRMEducationAdoption and GovernanceChange ManagementDynamics 365 University TrainingDesign-Your-Own TrainingUpcoming TrainingsWebinars on DemandAdd-OnsMarketing AutomationProductivityCase StudiesBlog & More
Latest Blog Posts
Tier 1 Environment Changes to Dynamics 365 F&O Licensing Microsoft recently announced that Tier 1 environments will not be included in the purchase of certain Dynamics 365 applications - read this blog to learn more.
FSI Blog Series, Part II: Sales and Marketing Collaboration In part 2 of our strategic partnership blog series, we discuss the tools and strategies that will help financial services sales and marketing teams collaborate better.
Deactivation of Configuration Keys in Dynamics 365 Deactivating configuration keys should be a decision carefully. In this blog we walk through what to consider and the steps to deactivation!
Read the Blog
Latest PO TV Videos
PowerInsurance is the Dynamics 365 Accelerator for Insurance Carriers Watch the video to learn about PowerInsurance, PowerObjects’ Dynamics 365 Accelerator for Insurance carriers.
PowerCapital is the Dynamics 365 Accelerator for Capital Markets Firms Watch the video to learn about PowerCapital, PowerObjects’ Dynamics 365 Accelerator for the Capital Markets industry.
New Customer Care Tools for Dynamics 365 Users Watch this video to explore several new modules in the Microsoft Business Applications stack, as well as how PowerObjects’ Customer Care practice has been committed to mastering what each can bring to an organization.
View All Videos
More...EventsPowerObjects offers a wide variety of Dynamics 365 events, trainings, and webinars.CareersWe're looking for bright, energetic and motivated people to help us leverage technology to solve business problems.NewsPowerObjects' latest press releases and Microsoft Business Application news.The CRM BookA Free Microsoft Dynamics 365 Training Resource
Contact
Privacy PolicyPowerObjects is 100% focused on Microsoft Business Applications through our four pillars of Service, Support, Education, and Add-ons.Who are we?We are PowerTeam LLC. (“PowerObjects”, “we” or “us”). Our registered address is 718 Washington Ave N, Suite #101, Minneapolis, Minnesota 55401, USA.We at PowerObjects are committed to safeguarding your privacy. This Privacy Policy describes how we may collect, use, share, and keep personal information about you. Please make sure you read this Privacy Policy carefully.What does this Privacy Policy cover?This Privacy Policy applies to our public-facing PowerObjects branded websites and other online services and will be available by a link on all sites and services which it covers.Other PowerObjects websites, apps, or online services may collect and use personal information about you in a different way and so publish a different PowerObjects Privacy Policy. We encourage you to take a moment to look at the applicable Privacy Policy, available by a link at the bottom of the homepage or as you download an app.What is in this Privacy Policy?What personal information do we collect?Do we use cookies?How do we use your personal information?How long do we keep your personal information?How do we share your personal information?Where do we keep your personal information?What rights do you have in relation to your personal information?How do we safeguard your personal information?How will we update this Policy?Other important information.How can you contact us about this Policy?What personal information do we collect?For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, references to ‘personal information’ mean any information relating to an identified or identifiable individual. Examples of personal information may include, for example, your name, your contact details or your location.We collect information that you supply to us when you choose to contact us for more information or when you register for one of our websites or online services. You may supply the information directly to us or indirectly by using your credentials from third parties such as LinkedIn or Facebook. This information typically includes your name, professional credentials, email address and other contact data. We may append information from other sources, such as Google Analytics, to supplement what you give us. We do, on occasion, obtain or license contact information from third parties for limited marketing purposes, such as maintaining an accurate marketing database.We gather date, time and certain additional information about a user’s browser and system or device configuration and capabilities, navigation history and IP address for all visitors to our web sites. We may use this information for our internal security audit log, for trend analysis and system administration and to gather broad information about our audiences. When you submit information through a form on one of our websites, we capture and store your IP address and email address. We use this information for website personalization purposes.Do we use cookies?We use cookies and other commonly used data collection technologies on our websites and in our newsletters and emails to collect information on both an aggregate and individual basis. Please see our Cookies Policy for more details on how we use cookies and how to control cookies or their use for targeted advertising or marketing.How do we use your personal information?We may use personal information we collect to:provide and administer our services;understand our audience and improve how our websites work;contact you and answer your questions;market and advertise our products and services to you;allow you to publish comments and participate in professional web-based forums;keep our systems, users, employees and services safeprovide you with the information or support you requested.How long do we keep your personal information?We keep your personal information for so long as is necessary in light of the purpose for which it was originally collected or lawfully further processed. The criteria we use to determine the period of time for which your personal information may be kept include:the nature and type of personal information that you provide to us;the purpose for which you provide your personal information to us; andnecessary business and operational requirements to continue to supply you with the services or functionality you have requested.We may retain your information for a longer time period if we are required to do so by law.How do we share your personal information?We may disclose personal information about you to third parties, including:to other members of the HCL group of companies;to vendors that work on our behalf;to law enforcement when we have a good-faith belief that it is necessary to comply with a court order, ongoing judicial proceeding, or other legal process served on us;to exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; andto protect human safety or our networks or property, or as part of a sale or merger of our company or business assets.Where do we keep your personal information?We collect, store, and process information on servers around the world and may access that information globally. If you are located in the European Union, please note that your personal information may be transferred out of, or stored outside, the European Economic Area. The privacy protections in these jurisdictions may not be equivalent to those in Europe. We will take steps to ensure that your personal information continues to be protected through adequate safeguards, copies of which are available from us on request at the email address below.What rights do you have in relation to your personal information?European law gives individuals a number of rights in relation to their personal information. These include the right to access, and in some circumstances to amend, delete, or restrict the continued processing of, personal information. Please note that deleting your information or restricting the continued processing of your information may limit our ability to continue to provide our websites, applications, and online services to you.You also have a choice about:Whether to receive email marketing messages from us. You may opt out of our email marketing lists by following the opt-out directions at the bottom of our promotional emails. Please note that we have a number of brands and products and allow you to opt out selectively. To remove a specific email address from all PowerObjects email marketing, send a request to support@hcl-powerobjects.com.Whether to share information about yourself and your use of our sites with third parties including social media sites.If you join one of our online communities, such as https://powerobjects.com/blog/, your comments as well as certain information about you may be visible to other members of the community. Please take a moment to understand how each forum works and what choices you have.If you use credentials from a third party, like Facebook, to register, then that third party will also record the fact that you have registered for our sites and may use that information consistent with its own privacy statements and practices. If you use Share, Like or similar social media buttons, those actions may be posted elsewhere (such as on the relevant social media sites).Whether to allow certain uses of cookies and other data collection technologies. Please see our Cookies Policy.If you have any questions about your rights, please email us at support@hcl-powerobjectsdev.comYou can also contact your local Data Protection Authority.How do we safeguard your personal information?We use a range of security measures to protect your personal information. Please be aware, however, that PowerObjects cannot guarantee that third parties will safeguard your personal information in a similar manner. Unencrypted information – including information sent via E-mail – may also be able to be read by third parties. As a user of our services, you are responsible for protecting the information you provide, including user name and passwords, from misuse, by encryption or other means.How will we update this Policy?We are constantly working to develop new services. We may also change our practices over time as our business and technology evolve, and this may involve changes to the ways in which we collect, process and use your information. As a result, we may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time.If we materially change our Privacy Policy, we will take steps to inform you of the change. We may do this through email, SMS, notices on our websites or other means (or a combination of these means). If you continue to use our websites, applications, and online services after the date any revised Privacy Policy comes into effect, you will be deemed to have read and agreed to the revised Privacy Policy.The “Effective Date” at the top of this Privacy Policy shows when it was last updated.Other important informationOur sites contain links to other websites not owned by PowerObjects. We do not control the content or privacy practices of those sites.Our websites and offerings are directed to people in their business or professional capacities.They are not intended for children under 13 years of age. We do not knowingly solicit information online from, or market online to, children under 13 years of age.We process personal information on the basis of your consent, except when you enter into a contract for the provision of services, or when we have other legitimate interest based on your interaction with us. You have the right to withdraw consent at any time, but this will not affect any prior processing of your personal information.How can you contact us about this Policy?For questions regarding this Privacy Policy, practices of the website, or any other privacy issue, please send an email to support@hcl-powerobjects.com or contact us at the address below:PowerObjectsAttn: Chief Information Officer718 Washington Ave N, Suite #101Minneapolis, Minnesota 55401 USA
Connect with the ExpertsX
linkedin-squaretwitterfacebookyoutube-playinstagram
